<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BuckStar</string>

    <string name="americano_desc">An Americano is a shot of espresso that is diluted with hot water and completed with a light layer of cream at the top.\n\nAmericanos
        are rich, intense, and distinctive in taste. The strength of the drink is dependent on the number of espresso shots you add. For many, it is the ideal way to
        indulge in the smoothness of espressos while maintaining the consistency of a drip-brew.\n\nOne of the best benefits of drinking Americanos is the lower-calorie
        and nonexistent fat counts compared to regular coffee.</string>

    <string name="cappuccino_desc">Cappuccinos are made by layering a balanced ratio of espresso, steamed milk, and milk foam in that order.\nThis is to ensure the
        cappuccinos’ bold and rich flavors, as well as to maintain its thick, foamy texture.\n\nThis popular drink is known for the latte art decorations that are
        often drawn into the steamed milk foam.\nIt is also common to add flavored syrups and other toppings, such as chocolate powder, to further sweeten the deal.
        \n\nIt has been revealed through medical studies that a cup of a cappuccino a day without exceeding 180 ml. Provide excellent health benefits.\nSuch benefits
        include significantly preventing heart problems and bad cholesterol, while also improving digestion and maintaining healthy blood sugar levels.</string>

    <string name="espresso_desc">Espresso is not necessarily a type of coffee, but a way to make coffee. The difference is the amount of water used to make espressos
        versus regularly brewed coffee.\n\nBecause they are made with a shot of water instead of a liter of water per cup of ground coffee, espressos are basically
        highly concentrated coffee. Because of this, you can expect espressos to have a more heightened array of flavors compared to a regular cup of coffee.\n\nThis
        can mean stronger, toastier, and more bitter cups, which flavors that will be amplified depending on the coffee roast. Regardless, you can expect thicker and
        creamier textures than coffee, almost like what you see with cappuccinos.\n\nLike with other variations of coffee, there are health benefits when drinking a
        cup or two a day, and with the added benefit of having little to no calories. Espressos are packed with antioxidants, providing ample protection against
        infections. Drinking espressos every day can also provide a significant improvement in your concentration and memory.</string>

    <string name="latte_desc">Lattes are versatile in customization, anything from sweet to herbal can be added to them, and latte art can be added to complete the
        drink.\nLattes are similar to cappuccinos because they are also made with espresso, steamed milk, and milk foam.\n\nThe ratio of ingredients is what separates
        the two drinks; however: while cappuccinos have equal ratios, lattes have more steamed milk.\nThe ingredients in lattes are also mixed together instead of
        being layered, like what can be found in cappuccinos. Compared to cappuccinos and the many other espresso-based drinks, lattes are not very strong in taste.
        \n\nThis is because they are heavier with milk than coffee. Due to being milkier than their counterparts, they are sweeter than most coffee, though still not
        as sweet as you will find in mochas.\n\nAlso, while cappuccinos are frothy due to the milk foam, lattes are creamy and smooth thanks to the extra helping of
        steamed milk.\n\nA cup a day can aid in burning fat, and with more natural flavors such as beetroot or turmeric, you can improve your memory and relieve
        muscle aches.</string>

    <string name="macchiato_desc">There are two different ways to make macchiatos: more espresso than milk to make an espresso macchiato, or more milk than espresso
        to make a latte macchiato.\n\nThat said, macchiatos are similar to lattes and cappuccinos, and it is not uncommon for people to mistake the three for each
        other as it is.\n\nThe more popular macchiatos bear the most similarities with lattes because they are both heavies with milk.\nPopular drizzles to add to
        the creamy drink are vanilla, caramel, and hazelnut.\n\nThe difference between macchiatos and its counterparts is the order in which the ingredients are
        added.\n\nFor example, lattes add milk to the espresso, but macchiatos do the reverse: espresso is added to milk. In terms of taste, it is generally agreed
        that macchiatos are more aromatic, and are considered a fair compromise between the strength of espresso and the lighter touch of a cappuccino.\n\nThe
        espresso macchiatos have a generally bolder and richer taste than cappuccinos, while the latte macchiatos make for fair competitors with lattes in terms
        of sweet, creamy goodness.\nThe benefits of drinking macchiatos include preventing high blood pressure, maintaining liver health, and promoting weight loss.</string>

    <string name="mocha_desc">Mocha, which is actually short for mochaccino, is a top choice when you want to satisfy your sweet tooth needs.\nThis is another
        type of espresso beverage, and aptly named for its pleasant combination of sweet chocolate meeting the roasted goodness coffee.\n\nMochas are made with the
        expected shot of espresso and hot milk, but completed with chocolate additions, and whipped cream at the top.\n\nThe chocolate additions are typically
        syrups, and other sweeteners such as cocoa powder or sugar.\nMocha coffees often taste far stronger than cappuccinos and lattes. It is regularly mistaken
        as a stronger, more sugary latte with more calories.\n\nDrinking a cup of mocha daily offers health benefits worth looking into. A very generous, very
        crucial health benefit mochas offer helps with combating depression.\nOther great benefits to drinking mochas include keeping your liver healthy, overcoming
        insomnia, and keeping your bones strong. Due to the combination of coffee and chocolate, you can expect immediate energy.</string>

    <string name="iced_espresso_desc">Iced espressos are made by cooling the freshly brewed espresso with cold milk, and then served with ice.\n\nIced espressos
        are still espressos, so you can expect it to be strong and energize you as expected.\nCompared to the other colder coffee types, you can expect to get the
        most caffeine out of this beverage. Much like the other cold coffee types, an iced espresso will taste sweeter, smoother, and less acidic than its hotter
        counterpart.\n\nOne of the best benefits of drinking espresso, regardless of whether it is hot or cold, is the ability to drink it without adding anything to
        it.\n\nEspressos do not need the addition of creams, flavored syrups, or sugars, in general, to taste great and provide the energy you desire. There are
        arguments that drinking an espresso, hot or cold, is one of the better health choices you can make when your looking for that daily dose of caffeine.</string>

    <string name="sugar_desc">The classic way to sweeten your coffee.</string>

    <string name="brown_sugar_desc">Brown sugar has a richer flavor than white sugar, beyond just being sweet, which makes it a good complement to your coffee.</string>

    <string name="whipped_cream_desc">Whipped cream can be a perfect addition to regular coffee, espresso, lattes, macchiatos, adding sweetness and creaminess.</string>

    <string name="chocolate_syrup_desc">Mixing some chocolate syrup into your coffee will quickly turn it into a comforting and sweet drink, closely resembling a mug
        of hot-chocolate in taste.</string>

    <string name="cocoa_powder_desc">If you want that chocolatey flavor but with less sugar, try adding cocoa powder on your coffee.</string>

    <string name="honey_desc">Unlike sugar and other artificial sweeteners, honey has the ability to improve the flavour profile of your coffee while also bringing nutrients
        and health compounds to your cup.\n\nBoth honey and coffee are great for boosting metabolism, so when mixed together you get a weight-loss promoting morning
        drink brimming with antioxidant properties.</string>

    <string name="mint_desc">A leaf or two of fresh mint can really bring a refreshing, cool aroma and taste to your coffee.\n\nNot to mention how beneficial mint is proven
        to be as an ingredient, packed with antibacterial and anti-inflammatory properties.</string>

    <string name="vanilla_extract_desc">An easy way to adding a sugary-floral taste to your coffee while skipping all the processed sugar and added fat, is to add
        vanilla extract into the drink.\n\nAdding a small helping of this ingredient can add a heavy dash of richness and a more complex blend of flavours to your
        regular coffee. </string>

    <string name="cinnamon_desc">The warm taste of the spice mixes remarkably well with the bitter flavour of the coffee.\nIt\'s also an ideal topping for people
        interested in augmenting the taste of their coffee without compromising on calories.\n\nBesides, adding in some cinnamon with your regular cup, can bring several
        health-enhancing benefits to you like lowering blood glucose and cholesterol levels, helping in fat burning and acting as an antiviral to boost your
        immunity with.</string>

</resources>